WELL, THE PRESIDENT HAS
NUMEROUS AUTHORITIES TO ENSURE
PUBLIC SAFETY AND ORDER IN OUR
COMMUNITIES.
THE PRESIDENT HAS THE AUTHORITY
TO SEND TO THE NATIONAL GUARD.
TO SURGE IN FEDERAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
THE PRESIDENT HAS THE AUTHORITY
UNDER 287G TO DEPUTIZE
OFFICIALS ACROSS THE COUNTRY TO
ENGAGE IN IMMIGRATION AND
CUSTOMS ENFORCEMENT WORK AND
MANY OTHER TOOLS.
AND OF COURSE THE INSURRECTION
ACT IS ONE LAWFUL STATUTORY TOOL
AT THE PRESIDENT'S DISPOSAL.
I THINK THE MOST IMPORTANT
POINT TO CONVEY TONIGHT, LAURA,
IS THAT THE PRESIDENT IS NOT
GOING TO ALLOW AMERICANS,
AMERICAN CITIZENS TO BE RAPED,
MURDERED, MAIMED AND KILLED BY
ILLEGAL ALIEN GANGBANGERS,
TERRORISTS, DRUG DEALERS AND
PSYCHOPASTS.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO LEAVE OUR
CITIZENS AT THE MERCY OF A
DEMOCRAT CRIMINAL JUSTICE
SYSTEM THAT FREEZE SERIAL REPEAT
OFFENDERS TO STAB WOMEN IN
SUBWAYS, TO BREAK INTO PEOPLE'S
HOMES AND STAB LITTLE CHILDREN
TO DEATH IN THEIR BEDS AND TO
UNLEASH THIS RAIN OF TERROR ON
OUR CITIZENS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS NOT GOING TO
STAND FOR IT.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
STEPHEN AOC IS YOUR HER FAVORITE
TARGET APPARENTLY ON INSTAGRAM.
CHECK THIS OUT.
HE LOOKS LIKE HE IS ANGRY ABOUT
THE FACT THAT HE'S 4'10 AND HE
LOOKS LIKE HE IS SO MAD THAT HE
IS 4'10 THAT HE'S TAKEN THAT ANGER
OUT AT ANY OTHER POPULATION,
POSSIBLE.
LIKE, LAUGH AT THEM.
LAUGH AT THEM.